http://www.ibslgroup.co.uk/cookie-policy/

Privacy Policy
As you may be aware, the new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), comes into effect on 25th May 2018.
For us to be compliant we need to let you know about the personal data we hold about you, our legal basis for holding it and how your personal data is used.
Personal data we control or process.
First name
Last name
Job title
Company email address
Company telephone / mobile
Device IP address
We take your privacy seriously and will only use your personal data to ensure continuity of service and supply and / or to provide you with information on relevant products and services unless you object to us doing so.
Lawful basis for processing.
Our lawful basis for processing is ‘legitimate interest’. We have carried out a ‘Legitimate Interests Assessment’ and followed ICO guidelines to arrive at this decision.
Email marketing.
We send occasional product or service emails, but this does not exceed one per month. You can of course unsubscribe from these at any time by sending us an email.
Updated privacy policy.
For details on how we use your personal data and your rights under GDPR legislation please contact us and a hard copy can be posted or emailed.  The Privacy Policy can also be viewed on our website. Full Privacy Policy HERE
If you have any questions or concerns please reply to this email or give us a call on 0191 237 0444.
Sign up to our newsletter
Links
Contact Us
About Us
Terms & Conditions
Privacy & Cookies
Sitemap
Latest News
20 Years and Counting – SGS, ISO9001
After recently completing our ISO:9001 audit we are currently awaiting our new certificate #iso9001 #certifiedsince2000 #SGS.  Congratulations to John Hudspith and the team! ISO 9001:2015 certification is an integral part of an organization’s efforts towards the broader aim of sustainable development. The adoption of a quality management system is a strategic decision for an organization […]
Posted by Steven Renney on 22nd Sep 2020
Read More >
IBSL Supporting Wallsend Boys Club & Grassroots Football
IBSL are proud to announce that they are sponsoring Wallsend Boys Club U9’s Green for the 2020/2021 season.  This is the third season that IBSL has supported Grassroots Football and the First year supporting Wallsend Boys Club. Wallsend Boys Club has a fascinating and colourful 109 year history, originally founded by the Swan Hunter Shipbuilders […]
Posted by Steven Renney on 22nd Sep 2020
Read More >
Copyright IBSL 2020
-
all rights reserved
